(Sheldon:)All right. There's no need to bark at me.
(Sheldon:)According to the inexplicably
irritable nurse behind the desk...
...you're after the man who claims
to be having a heart attack...
(Sheldon:)...but appears to be well enough
to play Doodle Jump on his iPhone.
(Sheldon:)We have to fill these out.
"Describe illness or injury."
(Penny:)I dislocated my shoulder.
(Sheldon:)All right.
And "how did the accident occur?"
You already know that.
Cause of accident:
lack of adhesive ducks.
(Sheldon:)Okay, medical history.
-Have you been diagnosed with diabetes?
-No.
(Sheldon:)-Kidney disease?
(Sheldon:)-Migraines?
-Getting one.
(Sheldon:)-Are you currently pregnant?
-No.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure? You look a bit puffy.
Change migraine to "yes."
-"When was your last menstrual period?"
-Oh, next question.